NG Voice Drama: The Black Demon's End
This is one possibility, the crossing of two fates...
and the ending that lies ahead.
"Shit, I took too long getting prepared! Make it in time,
please...!"
I was driving to Kissoji from the Kujou Mansion. Right now,
it's past 8 P.M.
It's summertime, but the sky's already pitch black.
It all started with a report from Rose.
She was a friend of my late sister, Saya, and helps me in my
investigations.
After delivering her report on Kakuya's Game, she asked me
to help save a boy named Akira Kijima in her stead.
There's no way I could ignore the situation after hearing
her story. I got ready and headed off to Kissoji.
"(The Black Rabbit... Kijima's supposed to be here.)"
"Urgh...!"
"(It reeks of blood... I'm too late.)"
"Agh... Augh... Uaargh..."
"Are you Akira Kijima? The people collapsed at your feet
are your aunt and little sister, aren't they?"
"Were you the one that did that to them? With that
tentacle-like arm of yours...?"
"I sympathize with your fate. Rose did too."
"She wasn't lying. She really wanted to save you!"
"But your Bloodmetry was even stronger than she could have
anticipated."
"She was able to save your life, but your power ran wild
in the process."
"It destroyed both your memories and your humanity!"
"As a result, you're still alive, but your mind and body
became those of a spirit."
"With things like this, I can't let you be."
"Agh... Augh...."
"Unfortunately, my words don't seem to be reaching you."
"I really wish we could've met in a different way."
"Forgive me, Akira Kijima."
"I've already looked into you, so I've come prepared."
"Even if my voice can't reach you, this song should!"
"Under the clouds, looking for the stars..."
"Aaugh...!"
"Remember Kaoru Hazuki! Remember her death!"
"Next up is this can of juice!"
"Augh...!"
"How about that weirdly named juice?! Did it jog your
memory about Seiji Amanome's death?!"
"I know it's difficult, but you have to remember, Akira!"
"You can't escape the past by running away from your memories!"
"You have to face the truth to keep living!"
"If you can't do that, you'll be engulfed by your darkness and
become a real spirit!"
"Face the truth! There's no other choice!"
"I'll help you get through it!"
"Ha...zuki...? Ama...nome...?"
"Uagh... UAAAGHH!!!"
"(Agh...! The tentacle's... wrapped around my neck...)"
"(Let go of me... I can't... breathe...!)"
"Augh..."
"Tch... You really know how to get into trouble, don't you?"
"But y'know, Yashiki... these lead bullets work just fine on
these half-assed spirit wannabes."
"Oh, Mashita...! Sorry about that, you really saved me."
"But why are you here...?"
"Rose contacted me. Seems like that chick's mistaken me for
your babysitter."
"Augh... Aaauuggh...!"
"Looks like the little shit's back up on his feet. But his arm's
been shot. His movement's slowed."
"Hurry up and finish him off, Yashiki."
"Yeah, I know. With the state he's in, he might take a proper
look at this."
"Akira, you remember this hand mirror, don't you?"
"It's was your late mother Satomi's, wasn't it?"
"Seems like Rose found it in your room. She gave it to me,
thinking it might come in handy."
"She was afraid of what flowed through the Miroku family's
blood, hoping that you wouldn't encounter the same fate."
"But her wish didn't come true. You couldn't escape from the
curse running through your veins."
"But your life's not over yet, is it?!"
"Akira! Look into the mirror! Look at what you've become!"
"And reject it! Your mother never wanted you to end up like this!"
"Is... is that... me...?"
"Augh... UUUAAAGGGHHH...!"
"Seems like he passed out from shock. Looks like we're
safe for now."
"So Yashiki, what happens now?"
"Hm... We'd be in trouble if anyone came here after hearing
the gunshots. Let's grab Akira and get out of here."
"Got it. I'll contact the hospital. If we call them now, they
might still make it."
"You drag the brat to the car."
"I'll drive, Yashiki. You stay in the back and treat his wounds.
After all, you're good with dealing with brats, aren't you?"
"Well, I'm better than you are, at least."
"...and that does it."
"Ugh... Where... am I...?"
"Oh, you're finally awake, Akira. How's your arm?"
"I just performed some first-aid with some bandages,
so don't move too much."
"You might re-open the wound."
"...Who are you?"
"My name's Kazuo Yashiki. I'm something like a friend
of Rose's."
"Wait, could you be the leader she was talking about?
The one that uses crazy methods to solve spirit cases?"
"Ah, I guess so. That description of me is a bit concerning,
though..."
"I see."
"I'm already a full-blown spirit."
"Just look at this lame, squid-like right arm of mine."
"Because of my arm, Ami and Aunt Natsumi..."
"It's okay, Akira. They've been transported to the hospital.
I'm sure they'll get better."
"But still...! I tried to kill them! That's not something that
can just be forgiven..."
"Hey, gramps! Your job is to exterminate spirits, right?"
"Then please... kill me."
"...It's true that you've done something that can never be
forgiven."
"It's a burden you'll have to bear and atone for for your
whole life."
"But still... you didn't let the darkness consume you."
"You regained your humanity and came back to the light."
"If so, my job isn't to exterminate you. It's to help you.
I want to help ease your mind, even in the slightest."
"But first, it's time to rest, Akira. You can think about what
you'll do after you wake up."
"When that time comes, I'll help you out, too."
"Haha, you really are a nice person... but you're way too
naive."
"We're almost at the Kujou Mansion."
"Yashiki, is that brat asleep?"
"Yeah. Both his body and mind are in shambles. It's best for him
to rest for now."
"Even though he just looks like a demon when he's asleep."
"So, what are you planning to do after bringing that kid home?"
"I... want to do something to save him, Mashita."
"Don't tell me... you're seeing yourself in him, aren't you, Yashiki?"
"You both had your lives pulled around by spirits, losing your
family in the process. You two really are birds of a feather."
"I can't deny my sympathy with him."
"But we're not the same! His family's still alive."
"If he's freed of his curse and has someone to support him,
he might be able to go back to his normal life."
"Don't you agree?!"
"Tch. Easy on the brats as always, huh?"
"Just like during the The Departed case."
"But Yashiki, don't forget this: he isn't a human anymore.
He's a spirit."
"The amount of darkness a spirit is burdened with is always
beyond our wildest expectations. I'm sure you know that."
"Against all that darkness, that speck of reason he showed
you doesn't stand a chance."
"What are you trying to say, Mashita?!"
"You already know, don't you, Yashiki?"
"That brat's actually-"
"You're wrong, Mashita. Remember why we're doing this
work in the first place."
"...Yeah. You might be right."
"AAAUUUGGHHH!!"
"You bastard! Let go of the handle!"
"UUAAGGGHHH!"
"AAUUGGGHHHH!!!"